hotsportchannel.com 2012-01-23

# Barcelona vs Real Madrid 3-1 Highlights: Privacy Policy

###  [Privacy Policy](http://www.hotsportchannel.com/p/privacy-policy.html)

hotsportchannel.com, Privacy of visitors www.hotsportchannel.com is very important to us. 

Here is a little info about the types of personal information collected as part of the process of serving ads on this site, and how this information is safeguarded. No personal information collected is ever sold to third parties.   
Log file:   
As normal with most websites, www.hotsportchannel.com use log files, where data is located in the log files is collected and used. The information in the log files includes the visitor's IP address, ISP, browser used at the time of the visit to the site, the time you visited and the distribution of pages navigated on this site.   
Cookies and Web Beacons:   
Cookies are used to store information, including your preferences may be time to visit and navigate this site.   
Utilize third-party advertisements on this site to support maintenance of the site. The advertisers use technology including cookies and web beacons as part of providing advertisements on this site, which sends a third-party vendors (eg: Google Adsense) information including your IP address, ISP, browser used at the time of visit to this site, and in some cases, info on whether you have Flash installed. This information collected is usually used for geo-targeting purposes in order to display ads according to your location and your patterns of browsing when visiting this site and other sites. For example: Google makes use of the DART cookie for this. You can choose to disable or selectively turn off cookies or third-party cookies through the settings provided in your browser, or by controlling the preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this may affect some of your interaction with this site and other sites.   
www.hotsportchannel.com do not have access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.   
You should consult the respective privacy policies of third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.hotsportchannel.com 's privacy policy does not apply to, and we can not control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.   
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found on the website each browser.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us

Disclaimer  
We are just sharing free links available on the internet. For any copywrite issue please contact the orignal site or broadcaster
